<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Chem Show Pre-show Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>See you at ChemShow | Flow metrics you can count on.</subject>
    <textOnly>View Web Version


We look forward to seeing you at ChemShow!


In Booth 504, Badger Meter will be displaying a complete line of flow meters and control valves designed specifically to meet the needs of the chemical industry. We will have a variety of the core flow measurement technologies including: turbine, electromagnetic, ultrasonic, and positive displacement, as well as our high-precision valve products.


New for the ChemShow, we&apos;ll be featuring Smart Valve Positioners and Industrial Oval Gear Flow Meters. Read more below.


Smart Valve Positioners

with NEW Patented Accurate Linkage System


The NEW Research Control® SRD features comprehensive diagnostics tools.

Monitors for fugitive emissions
Delivers real-time performance statistics
Facilitates both proactive and reactive process management

Available with integrated network communications, the SRD is compatible with Research Control valves and most other pneumatically-actuated valves.


NEW Patented Accurate Linkage System for the SRD Positioner
We have designed a cutting edge linkage system for Research Control valves which provides a high level of accuracy while managing the rugged expectations of demanding application environments.

Industrial Oval Gear Flow Meters


Badger Meter Industrial Oval Gear (IOG) flow meters provide economical and versatile solutions for chemical dispensing applications.

Measures viscous and caustic fluids
Achieves high accuracy and repeatability in a wide range of flow rates and temperatures
Fits into tight spaces with a compact design, 316L stainless steel construction
Offers control system interfacing or local monitoring

Badger Meter

Booth 504




We would love the opportunity to speak with you about how we can to contribute to the success of your business.


Feel free to stop by our booth at your convenience, or schedule a meeting so we can ensure we have the proper staff on hand to assist you.



Contact

800-876-3837

infocentral@badgermeter.com

www.badgermeter.com</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
